hotref.com 2006-11-05

# HotRef.com: The world's leading online network for business and personals

|   |  |  Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:   
---  
* We will never rent or sell your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes 
* Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology.   
Please read this privacy policy to learn more about: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by HotRef.
  2. How the information is used. 
  3. With whom the information may be shared. 
  4. How you can access and change your account information. 
  5. What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by HotRef.
  6. How to contact us. 

**Information Collection**  
In order to become a HotRef member, you must first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to enter nickname and email address, and choose a password.   
**Cookies & Log Files:**  
Like most web sites, HotRef uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows HotRef to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site. One type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the HotRef site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the HotRef web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave HotRef. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the HotRef service, but is not linked to personally identifiable information in any way.   
**Information Use**  
HotRef.com offers online networking services for business and personals. The information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you safeguard the quality of contents that you may receive. HotRef is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.   
HotRef will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. These include a series of up to five welcome emails which help inform new users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from HotRef related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user in your network makes a referral to you.   
**Information Sharing**  
* Sharing Information With Third Parties:  
HotRef takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. 
* Communications Between Users:  
Many messages you initiate through HotRef, for instance a notification sent to a non-user, will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Other communications that you initiate through the HotRef website, like a referral, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with users who are permitted to be your contacts.   
**Legal Disclaimer**  
It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**  
You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your HotRef account, at any time by logging in to your account on the HotRef website and editing the information on your account page. To request that we close your account and remove your information please send your request to [support@HotRef.com](mailto:support@HotRef.com). Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with HotRef under your name. You will receive a response to requests within at least three business days of our receiving it.   
**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
HotRef may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personal information, we will send a notice to the primary email address specified in your HotRef account or by displaying a prominent notice on this site.   
**Questions or Comments**  
If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@HotRef.com](mailto:privacy@HotRef.com).
